Guide to the Henry Walter Papers 1950-2017 MS 3016
New-York Historical Society
- Series V. Print Matter, 1950-2001; 3.75 Linear feet in three boxes and 1 oversize folder
  - Print Matter (#176-199), 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 9)
    * ManhattanTrend, issued by Cushman & Wakefield
    * Textbook for a correspondence course in French wines.
  - Print Matter (#200-219), 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 10)
    * First numbers of various newsletters: from the Columbia Association (Italian-Americans) of the Comptroller's Office, Manhattan Institute for Policy Research's New York Perspective, Division of Municipal Supplies' DMS Happenings, from the Management Welfare Fund, Fiscal Flash from the Bureau of Accountancy, Borough President Donald R. Manes's Queens Update, from the Long Island City Business Development Corporation, the Jewish War Veterans Department of New York's Beacon, New York City Transit Authority's Welcome Aboard, Cornell Connection, from the Charter Review Commission, the Port Authority's World Trade Department's 110 News, and the New York State Museum's New York Delegate
    * City of New York Comparative Analysis: Financial and Economic Indicators for FY 1985, issued by Comptroller Harrison J. Goldin
    * Program for the memorial service at City Hall for Alfred T. Miele
    * Booklet of selected state bicentennial programs, Celebrating Our Constitution
    * An issue of Mobilization for Survival's The Mobilizer
  - Print Matter (#220-228), 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 11)
    * First numbers of various newsletters: Bureaus of Management Audit and of Financial Audit's Findings, Congressman Eliot Engel's Reports to the People, Jewish Community Relations Council's Urban and Domestic Viewpoints, Real Estate Board's Tax Watch, and Comptroller Chapter News
    * Issue of New York Delegate
    * First number of Skyline magazine
    * New York City Council on Economic Education's 1989-90 Fact Book on the New York Metropolitan Region
    * Port Authority's annual report for 1989.
  - Print Matter (#229-246), 1990-2001, undated (Offsite-box 26, Folder 12)
    * First numbers of various newsletters: BradyLine (1990), Manhattan Borough President Ruth Messinger's Dateline: Manhattan (1990), from the Comptroller's Office Quality of Work Life Program (1992)
    * First number of the Journal of Multi-Cultural Community Health, issued by New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation (1991)
    * Benefit booklet for pensioners of the New York City Employees' Retirement System (1991)
    * Three press releases from Comptroller Elizabeth Holtzman (1990)
    * Two issues of Rail Whispers (1991)
    * Metro-North brochure A History of Grand Central Terminal (1998)
    * Program for the St. Patrick's Day Parade (1999)
    * Issue #11 of the East Village Inky (2001)
    * Two bulletins from the Department of General Services (undated, but likely 1980).
  - Print Matter (#247-255). Oversize, 1980-1987 (Folder Oversize-small)
    * First numbers of Lexington Local newspaper (1980), New View magazine (1982), Westside Press newspaper (1983), Commuter Express newspaper (1984), Herald Center advertising supplement (1985), and Undercurrents: Life Beneath New York magazine (1987)
    * Special issue on top 50 cities in City & State magazine (1987)
    * Two copies of the Brooklyn Bridge Centennial Calendar (1983)
    * 14 prints of watercolors by artist Fein of buildings in lower Manhattan, apparently distributed by Bank of New York (undated).